[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_FreePrisoner_Yash_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"He would be proud, Yash.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes, and ready to charge into battle, always. I cannot say as much for our forces currently. Our positions are tenuous, at best.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_FreePrisoner_Russo_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Do I know you?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes. Captain Thorpe failed us... his greed sabotaged our safe passage, and set our souls on this course. Do you remember now?",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_FreePrisoner_Russo_TalkTo_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Continue",
        "NPCResponse": "I came here seeking insight into Isabella's affairs, but discovered little and found myself captured and tortured by her pawns.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_AttackMentally_Russo_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'll try.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "That is all I ask. Let us begin - I will read aloud passages related to her past. Words she once loved.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_AttackMentally_Russo_TalkTo_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"She's blocked me out now.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes, but we have proven today that she can be reached. It will only be a matter of forcing the channel open once again.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_HealAlly_Phaeris_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Why is my friend held prisoner?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Your passions are akin to Angry Earth. This is disquieting. You mistake our intention? This human is hurt. I… WE mend.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_HealAlly_Phaeris_TalkTo_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I have the Amber Lichen.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes, we are applying the lichen. Our contact with humans is limited. We forget they live their lives in much haste.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_HealAlly_Adiana_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"… probably stupidity.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Or is it that you've come to gloat? Humans do so love to spit upon the suffering of others.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_HealAlly_Phaeris_TalkTo_03",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'll leave when my friend leaves.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Oh, I… WE understand! We scent Cloud Moss upon you, what Mora-gaen needs, give it and she will be well, and we are pleased.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_HealAlly_Morgaine_TalkTo_00",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Morgaine! What happened to you?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "…..",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_HealAlly_Morgaine_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You were quite sick.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Sick? Nonsense! I remember, I was... worried, that's all, worried for my brother, and… for Aeternum. And something else…",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_HealAlly_Phaeris_TalkTo_04",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Do you know what Corruption is?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Oh… oh! The crimson poison... we know it well. Fighting this is how our sistren and brethren become Blighted.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_ReconnectHive_Morgaine_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Maybe this note will remind you.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Give it here. Oh, what is this nonsense! Deciphering my own notes is sometimes as difficult as understanding my brother!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_ReconnectHive_Phaeris_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Can they help us in the battle?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I… WE will ask. The connection is unstable, but I will persevere and try to express \"War\" and \"Corrupted\". It will take time.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_ActivateCrystals_Yash_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Continue",
        "NPCResponse": "If your ploy with the Angry Earth yields results, and Morgaine's gambit pays off, we'll have a large… and rather eclectic army.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_PlantBombs_Sun_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Continue",
        "NPCResponse": "Admittedly, this is more concentrated than I presupposed. I'll have to adjust the composition, but I can do so quickly enough.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_PlantBombs_Sun_TalkTo_02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"They'll explode when we attack?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "This will be my contribution to the assault on Myrkgard: blinding any reinforcements that might harry you, and distracting those that can still see.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_PrepareWarfare_Morgaine_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Continue",
        "NPCResponse": "With luck, our assault against Myrkgard will be a swift matter. This sorcery requires great concentration. Not easy to maintain…",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_PrepareWarfare_Sun_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Continue",
        "NPCResponse": "I have ever been one to linger in the background, the observer, but you have drawn out a new side of me. One that knows no fear.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_PrepareWarfare_Phaeris_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"No, your sense of self blooms.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Self? The Angry Earth are one, but we grow from dissimilar soil and in dissimilar ways. Perhaps I can be we, but also me.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_PrepareWarfare_Yash_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I appreciate it. Hold firm, Yash.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Oh, I will. I swear it! Never have I felt so inspired before. I simply wished to inspire you in case your morale falters.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_AssaultStronghold_Grace_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Grace! I thought you sailed away.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I won't lie - I was sorely tempted, but I decided a joyride along the coast was enough. Beside, I knew you'd be needing me.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "99G_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Continue",
        "NPCResponse": "I'm half-surprised you're here, not that you'd let me down, but I've noticed you never take a moment for yourself. It's unhealthy.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    }
]
